Hurry, hurry.
Who's here?
Uncle, let's go to the hospital
for a check-up.
He said he was too big
for us to move him.
He insisted on waiting for Chengcheng.
I brought my boyfriend to help.
Uncle, let's go to the hospital first.
You're Gu Yu, right?
Where is Chengcheng?
I've fallen, and she's not even here
to check on me.
Chengcheng, she…
Chengcheng is on her way back.
You're Chengcheng's boss, right?
Tell me.
Where exactly is Su Chengcheng?
Where was Dad hurt?
Why are you standing here?
Why haven't you gone to the hospital?
Why are you the only one who came back?
Didn't Chengcheng contact you?
Uncle insisted on waiting for Chengcheng.
I called an ambulance.
No need. Let's wait for Chengcheng.
Don't call.
Your dad's fine.
He's just upset
that Chengcheng lied to us.
Your dad wants to see her.
Su Chengcheng, Tang Qi,
and you, Lin Yuan,
including Gu Yu.
You all told me
that Chengcheng was on a business trip.
But two hours ago,
Chengcheng's colleague came here
and said she hadn't been
on any business trip.
She just took sick leave.
You were all just fooling me.
She's not at home
and not at work.
Where has she gone?
Come out.
FORTUNE
Uncle, Aunt.
As soon as Chengcheng got the news,
she told me to come here at once.
What's with you?
Why are you dressed like this?
Take off that outfit.
I won't scold you.
Dad, Mom.
There's something
I need to tell you.
Chengcheng got a filter
that can change her appearance,
but it's made her invisible now?
Chengcheng is inside this doll,
but without her outer clothes,
we can't see her?
Yes.
Whatever she looks like,
she's still my daughter.
It's okay, Chengcheng.
Let me see you.
Chengcheng…
Chengcheng.
Mom.
- Dad.
- Chengcheng.
Don't be afraid.
We'll find a way.
There must be a way to solve it.
Dad, Mom.
The filter blocked Chengcheng's voice.
She can only communicate
by WeChat or by writing.
If you keep holding her like this,
she won't be able to say anything.
Sit down first.
Chengcheng.
Tell us whatever you want to say.
You can write it down.
Dad, Mom.
I'm sorry. I've made you worry.
It's okay.
Don't be afraid.
How could this happen?
I've been reflecting on this these days.
The filter has always been unstable,
but why do I only
want to take off the filter today,
when no one can see me?
When everyone
could still see me,
why didn't I make up my mind
to take it off?
Even though I knew it wasn't right,
why did I keep using the filter
and letting it upgrade each time?
Everything with you is wrong.
What more do we need to ask you?
Don't delay our next interview.
Su Chengcheng, we know the result now.
You can go home now.
Ladies first.
Thank you.
I pretended not to care,
but in reality,
I've always been dissatisfied
with my appearance.
I wanted to look like other pretty girls,
not be ignored by anyone,
and gain the affection and respect
of people my age.
Because of my anxiety about my appearance,
I could never give up the filter,
which led to today's outcome.
The filter kept upgrading,
slowly devouring my true self.
Now, no one can see me.
It's us who have failed you.
Though we've always said
we didn't care about your looks,
we've always thought
you didn't look as good as your sister,
and it'd be hard for you to get married.
But we didn't mean any harm.
It was all for your good.
But we didn't expect this good intention
to put a lot of pressure on you.
Qingli.
Introduce a boyfriend to Chengcheng.
Your sister hasn't even had a crush
since she was little.
I know you worry about me
because you love me.
I've never blamed you.
Did the interviewer criticize
the photo I edited for you?
Isn't this outfit too eye-catching?
Do you think others won't dress up?
Everyone will dress up
to save face, spending all they have.
Are these skirt pants too short?
This is called healthy.
Looking like a stick isn't beautiful.
That's sickly.
Chengcheng,
I've always comforted you
not to care about appearance
and sometimes purposely
looked unattractive
to show that I'm in this with you.
But if I didn't think appearance mattered,
why would I do such things?
I'm also one of those
who created appearance anxiety for you.
Sorry.
During interviews,
I have judged people based on their looks.
Sorry.
Beauty products sell beauty.
I hope the Marketing Department staff
can not only work hard
but also have a good appearance,
so they can be persuasive
when meeting clients.
I'll return to the palace.
Goodbye, Your Highness.
As my sister,
you've carried a lot of pressure
regarding appearance
since you were little.
Don't just dress up your doll
and do makeup for it.
You should put on makeup and dress up too.
Look at you,
not even bothering to tidy yourself up.
Your face is oily enough to fry food.
Since you're at home unemployed,
you should study how to dress up.
Dress yourself up.
It's fine if you can't find a man,
but it's deadly if you can't find a job.
Being pretty isn't my fault,
so I don't want to say sorry.
But…
Sorry.
Don't be upset or feel guilty.
It's me who wasn't confident
or brave enough.
Now, I understand
I can change how others see me.
I really like the person I am now.
Chengcheng.
Mom.
Dad.
Uncle, Aunt.
Chengcheng is not alone this time.
We're in this together.
We'll definitely find a way
to remove the filter.
DON'T LOSE YOUR HAPPINESS
TO UNIMPORTANT PEOPLE
Chengcheng, let's sleep together tonight.
You must be hungry.
I made some late-night snacks for you.
It's here.
The gloves are for Chengcheng.
Thank you. I'm thanking you on her behalf.
No. Chengcheng would say,
"Thank you, my dear mom."
So childish.
Alright, eat then.
If it's not enough, I'll make more.
It's enough.
They can't eat too much at night.
It's bad for digestion.
Right.
Eat then.
Congrats to Su Chengcheng
for finding someone.
Thank you.
With you all here,
even if I'm invisible forever,
I won't be afraid.
Can't you drink?
Chengcheng must be moved
to have such a good friend like me
and such a beautiful sister
like you.
Tonight, I'll sleep in my room.
Let's eat, everyone.
Time to eat.
Wear the gloves to eat.
I don't want to.
MY MOM
My mom is invisible.
No one can see her or hear her.
Every time our family goes on a trip,
everyone can only see me and Dad,
but I know Mom has always been with us.
She loves me and Dad so much.
She often performs magic for me.
Tang Yuwen, you're lying.
You don't have a mom.
Yeah, you're lying. You don't have a mom.
- You're lying to us.
- I have a mom.
You don't have a mom.
- Tang Yuwen, you're lying.
- I do.
You don't have a mom.
You're lying.
- You don't have a mom.
- I have a mom!
A bunch of stupid kids.
Tang Yuwen?
My son is a Tang?
I married Tang Qi?
If I'm trapped by this filter
and remain invisible…
TANG QI
…can you really accept
an invisible girlfriend?
Are you anxious
about your appearance again?
I'm talking about being invisible.
That's different
from thinking I'm not pretty.
I guess this is the benefit
of being invisible.
Miss Su, may I ask if you're free today?
What could I possibly be busy with?
I'm free.
TANG QI
Half an hour later,
I'll pick you up downstairs.
Let's have a date.
OK.
Keep walking.
I had a dream last night.
I dreamed our son
was in elementary school.
Do you know what our son's name is?
He's called Tang Yuwen Chinese.
Why isn't he called Tang Tiyu Sports?
What are you talking about?
How did you know I was speaking?
Your facial muscles were moving.
Come on. Let's keep walking.
OK, slow down.
We're here.
For me, this is a special place.
The first time I waited joyfully
for the girl I liked.
The first time I felt heartbroken
for losing the girl I liked.
Su Miao!
Sorry.
I thought my vision was fine,
but I always ignored you.
This is something I made.
What is this?
When molten glass drips into cold water,
it'll solidify into a droplet
under gravity.
Named after the discoverer,
it's called Prince Rupert's drops.
It may seem simple in shape,
but its structure is special.
It's extremely hard.
Even when subjected
to eight tons of pressure
or shot with a bullet, it won't break.
It must be the hardest glass in the world.
It can withstand eight tons of pressure,
and even bullets can't shatter it.
But if you pinch its critical point,
that is, this little tail…
You just need to pinch it a little hard,
and the whole drop
will shatter into pieces instantly
and completely crushed.
As it is both incredibly hard and fragile,
Westerners often consider it
as a symbol of love.
This is the love you made then.
I will accept it.
Carry it with you when you go out.
Others can't see it,
but when you have an emergency,
you can pinch its tail.
No matter where you are,
I will be able to find you.
Your dad, mom, sister,
and Lin Yuan
will also be able to find you.
This time,
I'll never lose sight of you again.
Su Chengcheng,
will you marry me?
Even if I can't see you
and kiss the wrong place…
Even if I can't hear you
and won't be able to respond
when you cry for help…
Yes.
Even if I can't hear you
say yes…
Sorry.
This is your first proposal,
but I can't let you hear me.
Then I'll
let you feel it.
Yuan always talks about you guys.
I should've come earlier,
but I only paid
my first official visit today.
- It's my fault.
- It's okay.
We originally wanted
to wait for Chengcheng,
but she suddenly…
So, we couldn't manage it.
Aunt, Uncle, don't worry.
Tang is contacting the lab in Beijing.
With professional cutting tools,
they will definitely remove the filter.
- Really?
- Yes.
But it's special,
so Tang said it'd take some time
to arrange.
Those high-end experts
can even send such a big thing to Mars.
Surely, they can remove a bracelet.
Don't worry.
That's great.
Tang
is a reliable young man.
By the way,
I have a friend from the Qin Mountains.
I asked him to buy some local specialties
from his fellow villagers.
This is…
Ferns. So tender.
You can't find such tender ferns outside.
- Yeah.
- Good stuff.
This is…
I know this one too.
Walnut flowers,
also called longevity vegetables.
We haven't had this in years.
Hurry.
Go to the kitchen and soak it in water.
We'll stir-fry it tonight.
Alright, you chat.
I'll go soak it.
Alright.
These are wild mushrooms
from the mountains.
They just dried whatever they picked.
There are all sorts of mushrooms.
Smells so good.
I just bought a chicken this morning.
We can make a mushroom stew
with chicken tonight.
These are ginkgo nuts.
Ginkgo nuts.
I've been watching a show lately
where they eat these.
I'll cook them for you tonight.
I promise they'll taste better
- than what you saw in the show.
- Alright.
These are Chinese hickories
that my friend grows.
Yuan, take these to your aunt.
Help her clean up.
Some things are sensitive to moisture,
so package them up.
I'll help you.
Leave the walnuts.
Sit down and drink tea.
Drink some tea.
Walnuts.
I lost control and used too much strength.
Gu,
Yuan's last name is Lin,
not Su, like me,
but your aunt and I
have watched her grow up.
To us, she's like Chengcheng and Qingli.
She suffered a lot when she was little.
If you're dating, date seriously.
Even if things don't work out one day,
just be honest about it.
If there's anything sneaky,
making things complicated,
I'll be angry.
Don't worry, Uncle. I'll remember that.
Good.
Have some tea and walnuts.
Sometimes, women don't need to know
some things men have discussed.
Yuan won't know.
Eat. Try it.
Are these walnuts easy to crack?
It takes skill.
Decades of skill.
Give this to Chengcheng.
Give her more of this.
- Is it good?
- Yes.
You eat it.
Mom, I don't want it.
Please don't add more.
You eat it.
Just eat.
Cheers, everyone.
Come on.
Welcome Tang and Gu
to our home for dinner.
Is Chengcheng still here?
Eat more.
Come on.
Eat more. Okay?
Come on, cheers.
Thank you, Uncle, Aunt,
for preparing so many goodies for us.
No wonder Yuan always says
that the food outside is never
as good as what you make.
Alright.
Thank you, Uncle, Aunt.
It's fine.
Don't be so polite. Eat more.
OK.
Tang Qi, you should just
copy whatever Gu Yu says
in the future,
and you won't make any mistakes.
Uncle, I'll toast to you again.
Alright.
Uncle,
cheers.
- Let's drink together.
- Come on!
What did I just say?
Eat this.
Thank you, Aunt.
- Try it.
- Everyone, try it.
Here, have some of this.
The dried tofu is delicious.
I love you all.
Not mine.
It's not mine either.
Chengcheng?
I didn't bring it.
Chengcheng.
Is it the filter?
ANSWER
Hello?
Don't you like the filter?
No.
Don't you like doing whatever you like
and become more beautiful and charming?
I do,
but I like being myself more.
My friends,
my boyfriend,
my parents, and my sister…
They like me,
not Su Miao,
Fang Jin,
or Quan Shengtang.
I just want to be myself.
See you tomorrow night at the same place.
Don't be nervous.
Since she contacted you,
she must be willing to solve it too.
That stuff there is really great.
- Really?
- I'll take you there next time.
Great.
Are we almost there?
Yes, almost.
- Sorry, miss.
How could you be so careless?
I wasn't paying attention.
She can see me.
I can see you too.
You can see me too?
Can you see her? This is my girlfriend.
- Yes.
- My girlfriend.
Can you see her? This is my girlfriend.
- How pretty.
- This is my girlfriend.
See? This is my girlfriend.
Yes. She's really pretty.
Yes, we all saw her.
Your girlfriend.
Granny.
Seems like you really like
the way you are now.
Thank you for participating
in our filter experiment.
This filter is for you.
I don't want it.
I just want to stay true to myself.
This filter is powerful,
especially after this test.
It will be even more stable.
Are you really willing to give it up?
I just want to be my true self
every day of my future.
Then, give it back to me.
Goodbye.
Granny, who are you?
Your girlfriend no longer
has special powers.
Now, she's an ordinary girl.
I can rest easy now.
In the past, scientists thought
chameleons changed color
because of pigment cells in their bodies,
but recently, it's been discovered
that chameleons have a layer
of nanocrystals on their skin.
So, they change color
by adjusting the nanocrystals
to alter the light's refraction.
Qingli,
aren't you curious why it doesn't change
to a color like a rock?
I'm curious.
Go ahead. Tell me why.
When chameleons want to avoid predators
or chase prey,
they change their colors to blend
with their surroundings.
But most of the time,
chameleons change their colors
to send messages.
Since they can't hear or smell,
they rely on their colors
to communicate with their kind.
For example,
when other animals
enter their territory,
they turn to bright colors
like red or yellow
to warn them.
Just now, it was anxious,
treating us as enemies,
so it changed colors so often,
trying to hide itself.
To protect its territory,
it had no choice
but to turn bright to scare us.
Don't be scared. We're friends,
not enemies.
Is this the gift you want
to give to Chengcheng?
Don't you think it looks like a girl?
Sometimes, it disguises itself
and pretends to be flashy,
only to cover up its insecurity
and encourage itself to be confident.
Sometimes, it disguises itself
to fit in like everyone else,
instead of being eliminated by nature.
It's indeed like a girl.
I just want Chengcheng to see
that the world is full of diversity,
and she's not the only one who can change.
Even if she can't take the filter off,
she can still live vibrantly,
like a chameleon.
How considerate of you.
See?
I told you Qingli and Chengcheng
would love it.
Let me check the time.
It's not what I'm thinking.
I want to send Chengcheng a message.
Don't worry.
We've found the old lady.
There must be a solution.
The door has opened.
She's back?
Chengcheng's back?
Uncle, Aunt.
You must be hungry.
Let's get the rice.
I'm stir-frying some vegetables.
Get ready to eat.
Dad, Mom.
Chengcheng!
I'm back to normal.
My goodness!
- We can finally see and touch you.
- Dad.
- You bad girl.
- Mom.
It took so long.
- Sorry for worrying you.
- Let me take a look.
You bad girl, how dare you scare us!
If it happens again,
I'll really deal with you.
Mom, Su Qingli is threatening me.
Such a tattletale.
Alright.
Go serve the dishes.
Be helpful, okay?
I'll go grab the cutlery.
And you.
Take off this clumsy and annoying thing.
You look like a big bear.
Su, hurry up. They're hungry.
Alright, alright.
Uncle, how about I make the last dish?
I'd love to show you my cooking.
Yes, yes.
No need, you're guests.
- I'll do it.
- Alright.
Just bring out the dining table.
Mr. Gu, you're really capable.
Not at all.
It's all thanks to my weak peer.
Try harder.